<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
	<content contentuid="h6143a09-3f8f-4772-a44b-3cee411f5997" version="1">Rivers of Blood</content>
	<content contentuid="h3352ac6-ea19-4c31-9fed-be4c331ebf7b" version="1">Weapon of Okina, swordsman from the Land of Reeds.
A cursed weapon that has felled countless men.
When Mohg, the Lord of Blood, first felt Okina's sword, and madness,
upon his flesh, he had a proposal, to offer Okina the life of a demon, whose thirst would never go unsated.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8f89657-e742-4c2f-b005-ac6b1da6665b" version="1">Moonveil</content>
	<content contentuid="h0ceaa5f-8e31-417e-81c0-d5b536210863" version="1">Katana forged of glintstone.
Masterpiece of a Sellian swordsmith. 
Light enwreathes the blade when sheathed, explaining its Moonveil moniker.</content>
	<content contentuid="h26c6e4a-d200-48e7-845d-de6db7facc30" version="1">Ruins Greatsword</content>
	<content contentuid="hdd7eb4f-b507-4edf-b030-d98281421c31" version="1">Originally rubble from a ruin which fell from the sky, this surviving fragment was honed into a weapon.
One of the legendary armaments.
The ruin it came from crumbled when struck by a meteorite, as such this weapon harbors its destructive power.</content>
	<content contentuid="he523547-9cc9-4dd8-b502-dae1141a05c6" version="1">Ancient Meteoric Ore Greatsword</content>
	<content contentuid="h4a92112-b397-4e7f-ac1c-d3c0da6a85a6" version="1">One of the treasures of the ruined forges.
Greatsword of ancient meteoric ore, ending in a sharp point.
Fashioned from an excavated shard of an arrowhead that once was a part of the old gods' arsenal. A capable piercing weapon that excels at thrusting attacks.</content>
	<content contentuid="h77a77e3-ac7c-4ef0-86b9-53404a5741e3" version="1">Antspur Rapier</content>
	<content contentuid="hff5645d-2f5e-4fcc-aeb0-7d12789b65d7" version="1">Spur of a giant ant which has been fashioned into a rapier. The blade drips with scarlet rot. 
Scarlet rot is an old legend, of which Maleigh Marais of the Shaded Castle was a private believer. And indeed, he eventually found his own personal goddess.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1ebd5c1-d2bf-4f05-9eb6-12cf2561752a" version="1">Axe of Godfrey</content>
	<content contentuid="h059ca78-2ec5-4b7d-8a45-1ac8497722c3" version="1">Weapon of Godfrey, Elden Lord. It was broken in a battle fought as leader of the Tarnished during the Long March. This weapon is symbolic of Godfrey's vow to conduct himself as a lord, later becoming an emblem of the golden lineage. In the days of the past, a crown was warranted with strength.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8fb9db9-d82f-452d-bab2-cfaa9fb1093b" version="1">Axe of Godrick</content>
	<content contentuid="hca95af2-7255-46ee-a2a4-5061f7eeca19" version="1">Greataxe wielded by Godrick the Grafted. This golden battleaxe is emblazoned with the figure of a beast, representing the strength of Godfrey, First Elden Lord and patriarch of the golden lineage.
"I command thee kneel! For I am the lord of all that is golden!"</content>
	<content contentuid="ha2ef6d8-b864-4701-b634-85709575dd6a" version="1">Azur's Glintstone Staff</content>
	<content contentuid="h786feeb-0569-497b-9e10-217e3383fb29" version="1">Staff of the primeval glintstone sorcerer Azur.
Only those who have glimpsed what lies beyond the wisdom of stone may wield it.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4ef542c-ee34-4613-bf83-30f11adc8b5a" version="1">Barbed Staff-Spear</content>
	<content contentuid="h8bc21bf-d5f1-448f-831d-b8dc2fece11e" version="1">Greatstaff of Jori, elder inquisitor. The tip bristles with golden barbs symbolic of the inquisition's torture, allowing one to wield the staff as a greatspear.</content>
	<content contentuid="h4e4c4bb-8f0d-43bd-a449-4e1cb3c1167c" version="1">Bastard's Stars</content>
	<content contentuid="hc030219-906c-4a59-b8f6-abf3fd54a94b" version="1">Flail which deals magic damage, having been imbued with power by the remembrance of Astel.
Formed of the same many-colored star debris that comprised the form of the Naturalborn of the Void.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb9767d9-5cc1-4e38-be68-83e9cc428325" version="1">Black Knife</content>
	<content contentuid="hcefedf9-e58d-4c4e-a653-6bffd9fa5cd9" version="1">Dagger once belonging to one of the assassins who murdered Godwyn the Golden on the Night of the Black Knives. 
A ritual performed on the oddly misshapen blade imbued it with the power of the stolen Rune of Death. </content>
	<content contentuid="h13dde4a-e5fd-47ed-8b50-7092ac382bec" version="1">Blade of Calling</content>
	<content contentuid="h30ae939-14ff-439d-ba68-05dc96a07a45" version="1">Dagger given to one who set out on a journey to fulfill her duty long ago.
The power of its former owner, the kindling maiden, is still apparent.
The one who walks alongside flame,
Shall one day meet the road of Destined Death.</content>
	<content contentuid="hfab1029-8355-421a-bc3c-6c6085168d12" version="1">Blasphemous Blade</content>
	<content contentuid="hca047e0-b2e5-45b1-a9e4-2ade4f7d4619" version="1">Sacred sword of Rykard, Lord of Blasphemy.
Remains of the countless heroes he has devoured writhe upon the surface of this blade.
Now they share the same blood, bound together as family.</content>
	<content contentuid="haa478d2-552d-4666-93ab-6f0728a33425" version="1">Bloodfiend's Arm</content>
	<content contentuid="h1582f4b-46bc-4e68-8d18-d89c8bbcb5d1" version="1">Weapon used by the bloodfiends.
An arm pulled from the corpse of one of their kin, and wielded as a makeshift weapon.
Having been sanctified by a blood ritual, this armament is capable of spraying blood stored within when executing a strong attack.</content>
	<content contentuid="h332fd0f-c03f-42b4-8656-7eee52a9de81" version="1">Bloodhound's Fang</content>
	<content contentuid="h06c2463-8449-4b5a-afc3-c92b9a0ffcf8" version="1">Curved greatsword with a gently undulating blade wielded by
Bloodhound Knights.</content>
	<content contentuid="h7b439af-d3fa-43b0-bf46-711d793765a5" version="1">Bolt of Gransax</content>
	<content contentuid="hb296c91-53bf-43da-a963-e99055c483d8" version="1">Spear whittled from the weapon wielded by Gransax.
One of the legendary armaments.
A great ancient dragon, Gransax once rained calamity upon the Royal Capital - the only time in historical record that Leyndell's walls have fallen. This marked the dawn of the war against dragons.</content>
	<content contentuid="h87d1282-9ab8-4547-a95f-65f1e08a1066" version="1">Carian Regal Scepter</content>
	<content contentuid="h7f1947a-04b8-46e6-b5e5-15b3ebbd6764" version="1">Magic scepter of Rennala, Queen of the Full Moon. The glintstone is known as a Carian Blue, enhancing full moon sorceries.
Only those of the highest intelligence may wield this, the finest of all glintstone staves.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc1a782c-d3ac-447b-a383-086aeebb3b21" version="1">Cinquedea</content>
	<content contentuid="h4d31c5e-02e3-4727-bb1e-136fd294537a" version="1">Short sword given to high ranking clergymen of Farum Azula.
The design celebrates a beast's five fingers, symbolic of the intelligence once granted upon their kind.</content>
	<content contentuid="haa4f2bd-64c7-4536-a3b0-750565ed9c77" version="1">Commander's Standard</content>
	<content contentuid="he1a5b70-22d2-449a-b856-71780ba36554" version="1">A beaten red battle standard is furled around this time-worn
halberd.
Even after his lord was fled, Commander O'Neil continued to
brandish this flag in the devastation of the rot-eaten field of battle,
the sole veteran who remembers this battle with pride.</content>
	<content contentuid="h50fb855-dd84-4b4f-a50e-dee7b95a1c85" version="1">Dark Moon Greatsword</content>
	<content contentuid="h8a7937d-276d-4ae2-993d-b298e5a2e1f5" version="1">A Moon Greatsword, bestowed by a Carian queen upon her
spouse to honor long-standing tradition.
One of the legendary armaments.
Ranni's sigil is a full moon, cold and leaden, and this sword is but a beam of its light.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc06ce3b-c5ff-4cff-8e0d-1cda546e33ff" version="1">Devourer's Scepter</content>
	<content contentuid="hc16b485-c0c1-4c3d-8c04-496a45b9b455" version="1">Scepter in the shape of a serpent devouring the world. This weapon will one day become the very symbol of the Lord of Blasphemy.
One of the legendary armaments.
A vision of the future briefly seen by Rykard in his final moments before being devoured by the great serpent.</content>
	<content contentuid="h350494b-f89f-459d-a3de-26f81d3e847d" version="1">Dragon-Hunter's Great Katana</content>
	<content contentuid="h9cb4354-e8e2-4b90-8e9c-53a76bf224b2" version="1">Great katana with spines of gravel stone along its blade, wielded by the Ancient Dragon-Man of the Dragon's Pit.
Has an anti-dragon effect.
Formerly a Dragon Communion warrior, the Ancient Dragon-Man was once arbiter of those worthy to devour the Dreaded One.</content>
	<content contentuid="he4ce615-c08e-471b-b0d9-9a8c242800c2" version="1">Dragon King's Cragblade</content>
	<content contentuid="h97ea3bc-4cd9-416a-9e2a-6c31971f7ce5" version="1">Piercing Gravel Stone sword containing primeval lightning.
A portion of the Dragonlord's power, gained from a remembrance.
This weapon commands great power over the paltry, mortal dragons of today.</content>
	<content contentuid="h9dbb277-9b2d-4d55-b326-54c26e5708d6" version="1">Eclipse Shotel</content>
	<content contentuid="h7a86762-f835-4aeb-90cd-590af0579a3a" version="1">Storied sword and treasure of Castle Sol that depicts an eclipsed sun drained of color. One of the legendary armaments.
In Sol, the sight of an eclipse inspires a dreadful awe, preventing an onlooker from averting his gaze.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf9fb6e6-188c-4656-b02c-9cdac9d98fdc" version="1">Euporia</content>
	<content contentuid="ha3912d5-cc90-4e37-b204-ae00091c5507" version="1">Twinblade symbolizing abundance. The secret treasure of the tower. Though the blades, fashioned from golden shoots, are largely wilted and darkened, their luster can be restored by dealing damage to foes.</content>
	<content contentuid="h59d7bb8-8d4c-40ea-825b-191cb9ceb1ab" version="1">Fallingstar Beast Jaw</content>
	<content contentuid="h78fe2c3-1a58-49d7-99ea-6b0b0f0df34c" version="1">Part of a Falling star Beast's jaw, hard and shining black, fashioned into a weapon. 
With its sharp point, this colossal weapon can skewer foes. </content>
	<content contentuid="h1152745-8714-4ec0-b856-72f7c6c77ab1" version="1">Gazing Finger</content>
	<content contentuid="h52660eb-79f6-48cf-bd25-fdf51353c592" version="1">The head of Metyr, the finger-mother, wielded as a weapon without modification.
From within the center of the fingerprint that wrinkles the creature's foremost protrusion, a tiny wart-like eye gazes vacantly into the beyond.</content>
	<content contentuid="hbba6a7e-935b-4c91-ba1f-944a2d2428a2" version="1">Ghiza's Wheel</content>
	<content contentuid="he60358f-7077-40b2-a06d-9d2ff22fed62" version="1">Great iron wheel lined with flesh-flaying blades. Device of torture used by Inquisitor Ghiza. As the wheel spins it causes severe pain and blood loss.
The design was adopted for use as the iconic weapon wielded by Iron Virgins. </content>
	<content contentuid="hf1ea998-d52a-4139-9cf3-4c2fe0ac9bd2" version="1">Giant Crusher</content>
	<content contentuid="h24ab093-8fc4-4394-bd2b-4add2e8576bd" version="1">A hammer made from a boulder, used in the War against the Giants.
One of the heftiest weapons in the entire Lands Between.
After the giants were quelled, and man turned against man in violence,
this weapon was all but forgotten. Man has grown feeble in comparison to his forebears. </content>
	<content contentuid="h0481b22-a685-4589-93f7-2efef629a90e" version="1">Glintstone Kris</content>
	<content contentuid="hd03345e-59e5-4399-8b96-6a36c53914bc" version="1">Ritual blade once presented to Leyndell by the Academy of Raya Lucaria to celebrate their newfound peace.
Though the weapon is embedded with precious glintstones and features Erdtree ornamentation, the undulating blade is symbolic of an ancient ritual.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1def63b-4ec6-439d-b4df-a5304bf6903e" version="1">Godslayer's Greatsword</content>
	<content contentuid="h4119e3d-bb10-41de-bd3b-a78c7530f3ed" version="1">Sacred sword of the Gloam-Eyed Queen who controlled the Godskin Apostles before her defeat at the hands of Maliketh.
The black flames wielded by the apostles are channeled from this sword.</content>
	<content contentuid="hb4deeaa-1b5a-45af-bf6e-dcc91a371dcc" version="1">Golden Halberd</content>
	<content contentuid="h575042f-22bd-44ec-b63f-c74668c9778f" version="1">Weighty halberd forged of gold. Wielded by the Order of Tree Sentinels, heavily equipped knights.
A masterfully crafted weapon that lives up to its heft, but is difficult for one mere human strength to wield.</content>
	<content contentuid="h97c3704-6585-494c-8a91-4abb4eb3fbce" version="1">Golden Order Greatsword</content>
	<content contentuid="h71cd93e-ab31-471d-82f6-e9a7deb5705a" version="1">Greatsword made of light, modeled after the Elden Ring itself.
Forged by King Consort Radagon to proudly symbolize the tenets of the Golden Order.
One of the legendary armaments.
Telltale signs betray that this was once the greatsword bequeathed to him by his first wife, Rennala.</content>
	<content contentuid="h788ac91-3f6b-4ac0-a341-a291a0be90a5" version="1">Grafted Blade Greatsword</content>
	<content contentuid="h1e12dff-6fd0-42d7-ba86-6b76217adf3f" version="1">The storied sword of Castle Morne. A revenger's weapon, it is burdened with oceans of anger and regret. 
One of the legendary armaments. 
A lone surviving champion from a country now vanished was so determined to continue fighting that he claimed the swords of an entire clan of warriors.</content>
	<content contentuid="h04e9864-85f1-44fa-bc79-52022c8e30c0" version="1">Greatsword of Damnation</content>
	<content contentuid="h9cfb62e-e77b-4071-81d1-21f67656b28c" version="1">Golden greatsword that once pierced the body of Midra, master of the manse. Used by the hornsent in the execution of a damnation like no other.
The barbs that pierce the victim from within wind gently around the blade.</content>
	<content contentuid="h58e8022-c5a3-4278-a069-ccc5fbd506d5" version="1">Halo Scythe</content>
	<content contentuid="h54a5e8b-60e1-4ec8-b8bd-b15b727d844b" version="1">War scythe of the Cleanrot Knights who fought alongside Malenia, Blade of Miquella.
This was the weapon of commanders in Malenia's army.</content>
	<content contentuid="h094d7b7-239e-498c-baba-7fc2476bddae" version="1">Hand of Malenia</content>
	<content contentuid="heb02fb6-01f9-40b4-8dd1-d5688da4193d" version="1">Blade built into Malenia's prosthetic arm.
Through consecration it is resistant to rot.
Malenia's war prosthesis symbolized her victories.
Some claim to have seen wings when the weapon was raised aloft;
wings of fierce determination that have never known defeat.</content>
	<content contentuid="hab49e0f-24fa-487b-8503-78114d752353" version="1">Hoslow's Petal Whip</content>
	<content contentuid="hec6e08b-3b9f-49b2-a0af-07025e232a17" version="1">Metal whip formed of razor-sharp chain-link blades that have the appearance of flower petals. This work of art is handed down though the generations of the illustrious House Hoslow. High dexterity is required to wield this weapon, but it excels at inflicting devastating blood loss.
"The tale of House Hoslow is told in blood."</content>
	<content contentuid="h6e9f979-0952-4cba-aab5-f94b7306254d" version="1">Icerind Hatchet</content>
	<content contentuid="h882b557-5793-4159-8781-c9658ff2cb08" version="1">A hatchet with a frost-coated blade. One of several gifts given by
Castle Sol in the distant north.
Known as "freezing fog," the blade is thought to be a dragon's
scale. Inflicts a powerful frost effect.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6b7b8c5-bbe5-4767-a161-a5363d63cd3f" version="1">Inseparable Sword</content>
	<content contentuid="h856d11b-c810-4ae1-9474-35f1b500ed69" version="1">Sword forged by compounding silver and gold.
A sacred weapon to hunt Those Who Live in Death.
The inseparable twins found solace in the Golden Order, the only institution not to revile them as accursed beings.</content>
	<content contentuid="h56e0636-0111-4e56-a639-e3eec9698adb" version="1">Leda's Sword</content>
	<content contentuid="h8d9df8e-ae16-4c9b-9307-50d53c37f83f" version="1">Light greatsword with gold inlaid. Weapon of Leda, the Needle Knight. Deals holy damage. Though polished to a mirror sheen, this blade still reeks with the stench of crusted blood that lingers from the cull of her knightly comrades.</content>
	<content contentuid="h73d3a8c-3c22-48ac-939a-1d9b28c4e6bc" version="1">Lion Greatbow</content>
	<content contentuid="h53cb55b-d3aa-4fd8-9584-e60dfab0bc56" version="1">Greatbow of black iron wielded by General Radahn. Decorated with a lion mane motif.
Imbued with gravitational power of the Starscourge, when used along with Radahn's Spear, it becomes a true weapon of a champion. </content>
	<content contentuid="h60cad11-c4ff-4daa-a72a-a53b15adf027" version="1">Loretta's War Sickle</content>
	<content contentuid="hd14e458-c2f2-471f-b8c1-f42ad0e69313" version="1">Intricately crafted silver war sickle wielded by Loretta, Knight of the Haligtree.
Originally given for service as a personal guard to Carian royalty, the weapon's blue glintstone has been replaced with unalloyed gold.</content>
	<content contentuid="h3fb4537-67c2-49ad-8eee-97d3b00b1bfd" version="1">Lusat's Glintstone Staff</content>
	<content contentuid="h6aee896-69b4-4069-a244-0e628e68a020" version="1">Staff of the primeval glintstone sorcerer Lusat. Only those who
have glimpsed what lies beyond the wisdom of stone may wield it.</content>
	<content contentuid="he2f45e2-10e4-47a8-b1df-eda4319812e8" version="1">Maliketh's Black Blade</content>
	<content contentuid="hdc7bb5a-9884-414f-9365-474e8089955e" version="1">Maliketh's black blade which once harbored the power of the
Rune of Death. A sad shadow of its former glory.
After a fragment of Death was stolen on that fateful night,
Maliketh bound the blade within his own flesh, such that none
might ever rob Death again.</content>
	<content contentuid="h00e0fb6-9969-4bd5-86c8-1a36316a275b" version="1">Marais Executioner's Sword</content>
	<content contentuid="h9463809-b90c-471b-8429-b326bcfa042f" version="1">Storied sword of House Marais, the family of executioners who presided over the Shaded Castle. One of the legendary armaments.
Elemer of the Briar, the Bell Bearing Hunter, snatched the sword from the site of his looming execution, and furnished it with battle skills from his home of Eochaid.</content>
	<content contentuid="hd928c3a-c94c-4031-af95-3ba73b0c2714" version="1">Marika's Hammer</content>
	<content contentuid="h7f27a9d-c2bf-4028-81b1-228ce82ad01b" version="1">Stone hammer made in the lands of the Numen, outside the Lands Between. The tool with which Queen Marika shattered the Elden Ring and Radagon attempted to repair it.
The hammer partially broke upon shattering the Ring, becoming splintered with rune fragments.</content>
	<content contentuid="h138318b-6d77-431d-bcfb-e4caf5535682" version="1">Milady</content>
	<content contentuid="hccfc7d9-21a1-448c-957b-c24020299463" version="1">A light greatsword; that is, a sword whose blade matches the length of a greatsword, while being constrained to a minimal weight. Nicknamed after ladies of noble status for its refined appearance. With cultivated form, one can wield this weapon as swiftly as one might a straight sword.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0a38938-e4ff-49cb-bfa9-711fa5e1b9ca" version="1">Mohgwyn's Sacred Spear</content>
	<content contentuid="h639adce-7389-46c8-b97c-8988ed0bcc6d" version="1">Trident of Mohg, Lord of Blood. A sacred spear that will come to symbolize his dynasty.
As well as serving as a weapon, it is an instrument of communion with an outer god who bestows power upon accursed blood.
The mother of truth desires a wound.</content>
	<content contentuid="h87ac349-21b1-4d7b-8c97-1103a2821862" version="1">Nagakiba</content>
	<content contentuid="h465b378-5249-4abc-84e0-b3cabbf98b2e" version="1">Katana with a ferociously long blade.
Signature weapon of Yura, hunter of Bloody Fingers.
Reminiscent of a reinforced spear, its imposing length can be put to good use with powerful thrusting attacks.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc868b36-4fe8-44ef-99f3-ddb73e3c0ffc" version="1">Ordovis's Greatsword</content>
	<content contentuid="he51126f-8c39-4e28-8099-1d734c4a1946" version="1">Greatsword of Ordovis, one of the two honored as foremost
among the Crucible Knights.
This sword is imbued with an ancient holy essence.
Its red tint exemplifies the nature of primordial gold, said to be
close in nature to life itself.</content>
	<content contentuid="h25d97b2-746f-4189-a94e-64770480f2d3" version="1">Poleblade of the Bud</content>
	<content contentuid="hfeefeff-8d02-4214-b8df-4e491b307162" version="1">Weapon of Romina, Saint of the Bud.
A scarlet glaive with a dangling bud-like blade.
Attacks cause buildup of rot.
Once, in the crumbling, burning church, Romina held the bud in speechless silence.
That bud would become her blade.</content>
	<content contentuid="h760b759-81db-4c94-a3e0-3b17302d058f" version="1">Prince of Death's Staff</content>
	<content contentuid="hdc9610c-6fce-4cf7-bcdf-c4bdc60d60d3" version="1">Staff embedded with sullied amber, said to be a very part of the Prince of Death. Enhances death sorceries.
One of the staves deemed heretical by the academy.</content>
	<content contentuid="hef8988a-6fbf-44e9-abd0-8e18a43981a3" version="1">Putrescence Cleaver</content>
	<content contentuid="h97fbfba-33b6-4763-8150-a34a217e0166" version="1">Weapon wielded by the Putrescent Knight. A great cleaver of hardened putrescence affixed to an arch fashioned from human bones.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc4fcc2e-0e30-4699-81f4-53f17042a2b7" version="1">Reduvia</content>
	<content contentuid="hcb95d11-0a67-450c-8843-011385a4eae0" version="1">Jagged dagger with a distinctive curled blade.
Carried by the noble servants of the Lord of Blood.
This dagger rips the flesh as it enters, inflicting blood loss with sickening efficacy. A proud testament to the success of its vicious design, this weapon is perpetually coated in blood.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6e0115d-749b-427d-87af-21dd1f31fcf2" version="1">Rellana's Twin Blades</content>
	<content contentuid="hc666da5-46a1-40a0-b212-22161ec0dde1" version="1">Carian light greatsword embedded with blue glintstone. Weapon of Rellana, the Twin Moon Knight. Two swords as a single armament. When two-handing, a straight sword engraved with golden flame will be carried in the left hand. Here, and here alone, were moon and fire ever together.</content>
	<content contentuid="h0d46506-527d-46f5-b650-5ae57ce5e723" version="1">Ringed Finger</content>
	<content contentuid="hbd0688a-456f-4e60-83e0-a8ca57e508eb" version="1">Bludgeon made of an enormous finger sheathed in several heavy rings. Thought to have been cut from an ancestor of the Fingercreeper.
Some life yet remains in this legacy of an ancient act of blasphemy, as evidenced by the barely perceptible warmth it still exudes.</content>
	<content contentuid="he72a5f8-b492-4cd8-bd77-4f2af8d5f058" version="1">Rogier's Rapier</content>
	<content contentuid="h435ab49-55c3-48f1-8c53-0d0fadb690ee" version="1">Piercing sword of superior quality, featuring intricate ornamentation.
Signature weapon of the sorcerer Rogier.</content>
	<content contentuid="hff5a928-d024-419c-a0f1-666eaafd9f19" version="1">Sacred Relic Sword</content>
	<content contentuid="he30a582-5525-48db-b510-f9fa4f872357" version="1">Sword wrought from the remains of a god who should have lived a life eternal.
Thoughts on what the weapon portends are many and varied. Some consider it the mark of a great sin, or a sign of great devastation. Some think of it as the end of an age, while others; the beginning.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8c825d2-2e14-4d0d-8aea-252765d5f69d" version="1">Scepter of the All-Knowing</content>
	<content contentuid="h741cdb2-36aa-4ff7-99bd-c11c6431a36f" version="1">Scepter in the form of a hand grasping a pearl. Signature weapon of Sir Gideon Ofnir, the All-Knowing. The pearl stands for the world, the heavens, and an eye, representing the many forms of knowledge, never fully attainable. Even knowing that, the All-
Knowing's hand grasps for it.</content>
	<content contentuid="h39b710f-ce9a-4fc7-a5cf-f3588e9731ef" version="1">Serpent-Hunter</content>
	<content contentuid="h510fe06-7b9f-41fb-97af-70ef91a07975" version="1">Weapon that serves as both greatsword and spear. Thought to have been used to hunt an immortal great serpent in the distant past, it manifests a long blade of light when facing such a creature.
When their master's heroic aspirations degenerated into mere greed, his men searched for a weapon with which they might halt their lord.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1471ab0-5a54-4ecd-9c48-3a10b12b5432" version="1">Shadow Sunflower Blossom</content>
	<content contentuid="ha377469-ade3-4521-a778-9092a8187cb7" version="1">The head of a monstrous shadow sunflower manifestation of the Scadutree. Then again, it might be just a flower, wielded as a weapon. Much like the Scadutree itself in appearance, a second stalk winds tightly around the first, almost as if in a tender embrace.</content>
	<content contentuid="h36ff3e2-8663-42d9-a8e8-997e34e9a09c" version="1">Siluria's Tree</content>
	<content contentuid="hd796364-d45c-43b8-9205-d66b04b9d3bb" version="1">Siluria's Tree, weapon of one of the two honored as foremost among the Crucible Knights.
The primordial form of the Erdtree is close in nature to life itself, and this spear, modeled on its crucible, is imbued with ancient holy essence.</content>
	<content contentuid="h106bfba-49f3-44ff-be7d-de2ac65dc49d" version="1">Spear of the impaler</content>
	<content contentuid="h4f4bf30-df29-46fe-9889-43517d6a5710" version="1">Weapon of Messmer the Impaler.
A greatspear with a warped blade in the shape of undulating flame.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf51c086-32f2-4c2c-bedf-0c1ccb205a70" version="1">Staff of the Avatar</content>
	<content contentuid="h149783e-5b07-4f61-a73a-06a1684526a9" version="1">Ceremonial staff depicting the Erdtree in its historic radiance. Wielded by the avatars who protect the Minor Erdtrees.
The avatars, emerging in the wake of the Elden Ring's shattering, were determined to protect the withering Erdtree's offspring.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcc8e3a2-4a3c-46c9-881b-ac9df609336f" version="1">Staff of the Great Beyond</content>
	<content contentuid="h8227987-7f20-44e1-bda4-cf5f4df14a8b" version="1">Staff fashioned from the tail-fingers of Metyr, the Mother of Fingers, and the microcosm raised aloft over the crux they form.
The Mother received signs from the Greater Will from the beyond of the microcosm. Despite being broken and abandoned, she kept waiting for another message to come.</content>
	<content contentuid="h795fa6f-ce08-43bc-afb3-a4b0c7345c1d" version="1">Starscourge Greatsword</content>
	<content contentuid="he15093a-b4f8-4ed5-962b-d7c68c44d53e" version="1">Curved greatswords of black steel wielded by General Radahn. A pair of weapons decorated with a lion mane motif.
Radahn earned considerable renown as the Starscourge in his youth, and it is said that it was during this time he engraved the gravity crest upon these blades. </content>
	<content contentuid="hbea8314-a4a3-4166-8515-9d10bcf04ac0" version="1">Sword Lance</content>
	<content contentuid="hfb72cdf-1d28-42aa-92fd-ce46e2a057e3" version="1">Weapon once wielded by Commander Gaius. A combination of greatsword and lance. Weighty and capable of being brought to bear with great force, this armament shows its true potential when used astride a mount. Gaius himself was never without his boar.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf684631-c5d6-48bb-9989-302670c534e5" version="1">Sword of Darkness</content>
	<content contentuid="h841a3f3-a689-4b5d-8227-21f06604c5e8" version="1">Sword of darkness, pulled from its stone scabbard at an altar. From the quick of the root, wandering coils of darkness coalesce and release, their eddies and vortices giving form to the dark blade.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6f9b183-8b96-4315-8cb5-1bad64cc4620" version="1">Sword of Light</content>
	<content contentuid="hf888769-5a0c-4e96-a8c0-b5ed511fbaac" version="1">Sword of light, pulled from its stone scabbard at an altar. From the quick of the root, unswerving rays of light intersect and reflect to give the silver blade form.</content>
	<content contentuid="he11f7e5-487a-4270-8036-80e4b803503e" version="1">Sword of Milos</content>
	<content contentuid="heaa59bb-684f-473d-a210-8db6bbcef39a" version="1">Sinister greatsword fashioned from a giant's backbone.
Metes out wounds like a lopsided saw-blade.
Milos was undersized for a giant, and was viewed as sullied and terribly grotesque.</content>
	<content contentuid="hcfba1bb-77cd-466e-97e6-f219170d49e9" version="1">Sword of Night and Flame</content>
	<content contentuid="h2ffb7ec-24a6-4067-9edf-b5df5a8208ca" version="1">Storied sword and treasure of Caria Manor.
One of the legendary armaments.
Astrologers, who preceded the sorcerers, established themselves in mountaintops that nearly touched the sky, and considered the Fire Giants their neighbors.</content>
	<content contentuid="hbb6fff4-15ca-438b-ab98-d18a62756ecc" version="1">Tooth Whip</content>
	<content contentuid="h96122d5-8877-496a-8494-0dd7c7594368" version="1">Whip bestrewn with rotting, misshapen teeth.
Filthy and seething with disease, the teeth are embedded in the whip and dose the victim with deadly poison upon each strike. As the wounds ripen they grow inflamed and ooze pus.
The flesh of shamans was said to meld harmoniously with others.</content>
	<content contentuid="h8591b9a-e023-4e55-af7a-db0ea3cf6535" version="1">Velvet Sword of St. Trina</content>
	<content contentuid="h4fdc21e-08e7-4b84-9195-5dddce3b655d" version="1">Silver sword of St. Trina, now stained the color of velvet. When St. Trina was abandoned, the faint, light-purple mists coalesced into an intoxicating deep-purple cloud.</content>
	<content contentuid="h338058e-86e5-4659-b5c3-51f19a6694fd" version="1">Vyke's War Spear</content>
	<content contentuid="ha344458-7319-49c7-8a73-8c9516b6dc22" version="1">War spear singed and blistered by fingers, used by Vyke, Knight of the Roundtable Hold.
Like Vyke himself, it has been tormented by the yellow flame of frenzy from within.</content>
	<content contentuid="h3b51c2c-cc65-4e52-b4c1-62b56669f829" version="1">Watchdog's Staff</content>
	<content contentuid="hc69435b-3d7f-473d-88de-033fec22129e" version="1">Large stone staff embedded with glintstone. Wielded by Erdtree Burial Watchdogs who protect catacombs.
The Watchdogs, battered and broken over their lengthy tenure, rule the catacombs and are even said to command the imps.</content>
	<content contentuid="hc30d519-c0e3-421f-b4ec-75b436829c36" version="1">Wing of Astel</content>
	<content contentuid="hd1ad5d4-6bc5-4a89-a5c7-c80dd4d37f01" version="1">Sword fashioned from a delicate wing, suffused with the magic of
the stars.
Crafted from a relic of the Naturalborn of the Void who is said to
have assailed the Eternal City.</content>
</contentList>
